不! 不! 不!
No! No! No! No! No!
- 不! 不! 不要! - 去死吧!
- No! No! No! No! No! - Die!
《隔山有眼2》
两年前一个美国家庭横穿沙漠时 误入了一个称为16区的军事地区
到第二天破晓时 半数家庭成员被屠杀
在接下去的几周内 军方对 整个地区进行了搜索和摧毁行动
最近 由于某些未被公开的原因 电子监控装置被要求安装在这里
安装工作几乎到位…
雷丁上校 现在有活干了
Colonel Redding. Now there's a piece of work.
我简直不能相信他 让咱们在这鬼地方布线!
I can 't believe he's having us wire up this hellhole.
他在关注什么东西
He's obsessed with something.
在那下面他还想找到什么? 矿工的鬼魂?
What's he expecting to find down there? Ghosts of old miners?
他们在这儿
They're here.
嘿
Hey.
准备好做测试了?
You ready to test?
好的 每个都有信号了吗?
All right. You got everybody?
一号没反应
Number one's dead.
现在呢?
How about now?
可以了
Good there.
那做安全人员的假人呢?
How about the security dummies?
也没有反应
They're dead, too.
等一下
Hold on.
这到底怎么回事?
What the hell?
你发现什么了?
What you got?
我这儿全都是误读信号 准备好!
I got a shitload of false readings. Stand by.
再说一遍? 这儿发生了什么事?
Again? What's going on here?
他妈的!
Damn it.
没有反馈信号了
We just lost our feed.
我去查一下主连接点
I'll go check the main junction.
下面有点阴森森的 是吧? 50年来我们是第一批来这儿的
Spooky down there, isn 't it? We're the first ones in there since the 50s.
可能有鬼出没
Maybe it is haunted.
还好是你在那儿 而不是我
Glad it's you and not me in there.
操!
Oh, fuck!
连接盒出了什么问题?
What's with the junction box?
老毛病了
It's history.
又是老鼠搞的鬼
Our friends the rats again.
它们喜欢绝缘线的味道
They love the taste of the insulation.
好吧 我给基地打电话 一小时左右能把备用材料拿来
All right, I'll call base, should be able to get a backup here in an hour or so.
妈的!
Shit.
威尔森博士 你看见福斯特了吗?
Dr. Wilson, have you seen Foster?
正在山顶上校准红外传感器呢
Calibrating the infrared sensor up top the mountain.
- 他妈的笨蛋! - 对不起 雷丁上校
- Dumb sons-a-bitches. - Sorry, Colonel Redding.
没有陪同人员不能待在那儿!
Guys aren't supposed to be here without a goddamn escort!
威尔森
Wilson.
威尔森?
Wilson?
威尔森 回答
Wilson, come in.
这些家伙都跑哪儿去了?
Where are these guys?
汉 能听到么 是我福斯特
Han, do you read me? It's Foster.
汉 请回答
Han, come in.
汉 我是福斯特
Han, it's Foster.
嗨!
Hi.
你迷路了吗?
Are you lost?
我是福斯特博士
My name is Dr. Foster.
你叫什么名字?
Do you have a name?
- 块抛! - 块抛?
- Roonawee. - Roonwee?
- 块抛! - 快跑?
- Roonawee! - Run away?
福斯特?
Foster?
福斯特!
Foster!
你现在在哪儿? 快回答
Now where are you? Come on.
快出来
Come out of your holes.
快点 你个操蛋! 狗娘养的!
Come on, you cocksucker motherfucker sons-a-bitches!
福斯特!
Foster!
(坎大哈)
- 妈的 - 上帝呀
- Oh, shit. - Oh, my God.
快! 快! 出发! 出发! 快!
Go! Go! Move out! Move out! Go!
- 别停下! 别停… - 快!
- Keep moving! Keep mo... - Go!
妈的!
Oh, shit!
- 掩护! - 快 克朗克!
- Take cover! - Come on, Crank!
- 斯皮特! - 别管那个了!
- Spitter! - Leave it!
我得拿上我的头盔
I got to get my helmet.
斯皮特 别管他妈的头盔了! 快回到这儿来!
Spitter, forget your fucking helmet! Get back here!
不该这么糟糕的!
It's not supposed to be this bad!
去死吧! 美国婊子养的!
Die! America's mothers suck cocks!
- 你他妈的刚才说什么? - 你们美国人的老娘都是婊子!
- What the fuck did you say? - Your American mothers suck cocks.
我操你! 美国头号婊子!
Fuck you! America number one, bitch!
克朗克 不!
Crank, no!
- 克朗克! - 我们走 伙计们!
- Crank! - Let's move, pussies!
克朗克 你个混蛋! 别胡闹!
Crank, you dumb motherfucker! Don't freak out!
- 快 快 快 快 快! - 回来!
- Go, go, go, go, go! - Get back!
我知道该做什么 闪开
I know what to do, get out of the way.
- 给他做掩护! - 我知道怎么办! 我知道怎么办!
- Give him some cover! - I got this! I got this!
你出去! 这是真主的堡垒!
You get out! This is fortress of Allah!
快点 拿破仑 把门踹开!
Come on. Napoleon, get the door!
- 把门踹开 伙计! - 什么? 我听不见
- Get the door, man! - What? I can't hear you.
- 踹开他妈的门! - 门!
- Get the fucking door! - Door!
这是万门之母!
This is the mother of all doors!
退后!
Fall back!
- 妈的! 掩护! - 快跑!
- Shit! Take cover! - Run!
妈的
Shit.
妈妈
Mama.
你杀了我的孩子! 噢 不!
You killed my babies! Oh, no!
你杀了我的孩子! 你杀了我的孩子!
You killed my babies! You killed my babies!
小心 小心她!
Watch out. Watch her!
- 我们不是故意的 - 不 拿破仑!
- We didn't mean to. - No, Napoleon!
轰隆
Kaboom.
哦 你们死定了
Oh, you're dead.
白痴
Idiot.
这可真是一次个人与团队 愚蠢的绝妙演出!
A stunning display of individual and group stupidity!
17个平民被杀 自身伤亡惨重!
17 civilians killed and yourselves!
我真是他妈的吃惊!
I'm in fucking awe!
科尔! 永远不许在没有掩护时 去取回头盔!
Cole! Never leave cover to retrieve your helmet!
头都没了 还戴个屁!
You won't have a head to put it on anyway!
约翰逊 别为了保护耳朵 就把枪扔了
Johnson, do not drop your weapon to protect your ears.
聋了总比死了强
You are better off deaf than dead.
梅迪纳 你又不是复活的兰博 (兰博是美国电影中的人物 极其好斗)
Medina, since you are not Rambo resurrected...
先给我把命保住了 再去冲锋!
do not charge while your head is securely up your ass.
那些莽撞无知的人就是这样死的
That's how innocent people get killed.
还有你 拿破仑
And you, Napoleon.
是纳波利 中士
It's Napoli, Sarge.
你还真是个杀手啊 是吧? 拿破仑?
You're quite the killer, aren't you? Napoleon?
几乎就把整个小队在六秒钟 之内炸上西天!
Almost got your whole squad blown to hell in six seconds.
对某个反战人士来说 这可是个惊人的数目
That's a mighty impressive body count for somebody who's against the war.
- 什么? - 噢 对了 你哥哥没告诉你吧?
- What? - Oh, yeah, your brother didn't tell you?
这位能说会道的老兄反倒给自己 嘴上贴了张封条
Pretty mouth here's got himself a bumper sticker.
上面写着"要对话 不要对质"
It says "Conversation, not confrontation".
这是什么意思?
What's up with that shit?
你反对战争 杜内斯波利? (伊拉克战争时美国反战连环漫画中的人物)
You against the war, Doonesbury?
不是所有的战争 中士 我只是认为总统撒的谎太多了
Not all war, Sarge. I just think that the President lies too much.
所有的总统都撒谎 你个混蛋! 他们的工作就是他妈的这个
All presidents lie, asshole! That's their fucking job.
是 中士
Yes, sir.
杜鲁门之后的总统都没讲过真话 不过你知道他说过什么吗?
No president has told the truth since Truman. And do you know what he said?
- 不知道 中士 - 他说反对 到此为止!
- No, Sarge. - He said that the buck stops here.
现在你们都吃了败仗 所以可以算作阵亡了
Now you have all failed combat and are therefore officially dead.
他妈的-祝贺-你们啊!
Congratu-fucking-lations!
现在都给我带上装备 在那分装备的地方集合
Fall in at that deuce-and-a-half with all gear.
我们会被部署到 阿加福山的靶场
We will deploy to the Agave Ridge rifle range.
到了那儿你们就可以为行动 失败做个了结…
There you can complete your failure of these exercises...
…一个个把其他人全都毙了!
by blowing each others' dead heads off.
中途我们要在16号区停一下…
And on our way, we're stopping at Sector 16...
…给在那儿工作的科研人员 送设备
to deliver equipment to scientists who are working there.
这可是个高度机密地区 所以不许随便走动或者跟人交谈
This is a top secret area, so do not wander off or talk to anybody.
现在你们这群可怜虫都给我上车! 快!
Now get your sorry rookie butts in the back of that truck! Now!
出发! 出发!
Let's go! Let's go!
快走 斯皮特 不遇上十万火急的事 你就不知道抓紧!
Let's go, Spitter. If I had some steak on a string, you'd move real fast!
(美国军方训练与测试基地 新墨西哥州 羽马平原)
(16区)
老天 这地方到底有多大呀?
Jesus, how big is this place?
大概1300平方英里 以前是用来试验核武器的
It's about 1300 square miles. They used to test nuclear weapons here.
那这儿不就有放射性了么?
Well, isn't it radioactive then?
军方说没有
Not according to the Army.
靠!
Fuck.
好吧 也许我应该感谢拿破仑
Well, maybe I should thank Napoleon.
像中士说的那样 我们都阵亡了的话 我就不会因为战争罪而被审判了
If we're all officially dead, like Sarge said, I won't be tried for war crimes.
滥杀无辜可是重罪
The killing of innocent mannequins is serious shit.
在我来的那个地方 死可从来不是什么好事
Where I come from it's never good to be dead.
啊 克朗克 你又来了 拿下辈子开玩笑
Ah, Crank, you're taking all the fun out of the afterlife.
- 你少提什么下辈子! - 这话说得好没情面 伙计
- Shove the afterlife up your ass. - That's cold, man.
克莱德 是吧?
Clyde, huh?
我还是孩子时也犯过这种错误 那克莱德还是你的哥们吗?
Made the same mistake when I was a kid. So is Clyde still your dude?
对 斯汤普 克莱德还是我的哥们
Yes, Stump, Clyde's still my dude.
斯汤普 那是她的儿子 好像有四岁了
Stump. That's her son. He's, like, four years old.
这可真够要命的
That is so fucked up.
死有一个好处 就是可以不用听你在这儿胡扯
One good thing about being dead. Wouldn't have to listen to your bullshit.
这地方就是这样 整个一摊狗屎!
That's all there is out here. It's a bunch of bullshit.
这鬼地方过去可很不安全
This bullshit's got a crazy past.
你们知道么他们以前拿这儿 做原子弹试验基地
You know they used to use this as a test ground for A-bombs?
"你们知道这儿过去是原子弹 试验基地么? "
"You guys know this used to be a test ground for A-bombs!"
谁他妈问你了? 爱好和平男!
Who the fuck asked you? Peace ass shit boy!
噢 对 不好意思 我忘了 我是在和复活的兰博打交道呢
Oh, right. I'm sorry. I forgot I was dealing with Rambo resurrected.
你倒是能让我的"蛋蛋"复活
You can Rambo resurrect my balls, bitch.
你个下流货色!
You with the pinche puta.
怎么 年纪轻轻就不想活了? 嗯?
What, you wanna die young, cabron? Huh? Huh?
我现在就杀了你!
I'll kill you right now.
克朗克!
Crank!
我曾经杀过一个人
I killed somebody once.
那很容易 所以杀人才那么危险
It was easy. That's why it's so dangerous.
我看那家伙一点也不顺眼
I don't fucking like that guy.
我可不喜欢在这儿忍受你们 但我会适应的
Well, I don't like being out here having to put up with you, but I deal with it.
你也要适应
So deal with it.
谢谢
Thanks.
别把克朗克放在心上 他就是一暴脾气的混蛋
Don't mind Crank. He's just a cranky motherfucker.
他们还真是绝密 根本就看不见 嗯?
They're so top secret, they're invisible, huh?
你说得对
You got that right.
哦 腿不听使唤了
Oh, leg's asleep.
- "鸡鸡"不听使唤了! - 想唤醒它么?
- Dick's asleep! - You wanna wake it up?
不 那是你爸的活儿
Nah, that's your daddy's job.
嘿 你们两个给我闭嘴 把那箱子搬下车 放到帐篷里
Hey, you two, cut the bullshit. Off-load that crate. Put it in the tent!
斯皮特 给我接基地
Spitter, get me base.
国民自卫队杨基59号 呼叫羽马平原基地 完毕
National Guard Yankee Five Niner calling Yuma Flats Base, over.
没反应 中士 因为山的缘故
Nothing, sir. It's the hills.
继续试
Keep trying.
国民自卫队杨基59号 呼叫羽马平原基地 完毕
National Guard Yankee Five Niner to Yuma Flats Base, over.
嘿
Hello.
- 大兵克兰克海德 - 是 中士
- Private Crackhead. - Sarge.
你看看能不能找到雷丁上校 他应该是负责这边安全的
See if you can find Colonel Redding. He's supposed to be the security over here.
看见这些电线了么? 它们都通向那里的旧地下掩体
See these cables? They run into that old bunker over there.
你去检查一下 要留神脚下
Check it out. Watch your step.
是 中士
Yes, sir, Sergeant.
大兵米奇 你看看能不能找到些汽油
Private Mickey Mouse, see if you can find some gas.
这附近某个地方肯定会有几桶
There's got to be some cans around here somewhere.
是 中士
Yes, Sergeant.
拿破仑! 你到底要去哪儿?
Napoleon! Where the fuck are you going?
- 我只是想上趟洗手间 - 你他妈又在开我玩笑吗?
- I was just going to use the facilities. - Are you fucking kidding me?
你现在是在进行山地遇袭训练 在坎大哈可没有马桶和洗手池
You are in Mountain Assault training. There are no Port-a-Potties in Kandahar.
你得能应付及其恶劣的环境 明白吗?
You'll take your dumps behind the cactus with the scorpions. Understand me?
- 没有卫生纸 我用什么呢 中士? - 用你的手
- What do I use for t. p. , sir? - Use your fucking hand.
是 中士
Yes, Sarge.
呦!
Yo!
雷丁上校?
Colonel Redding?
见鬼!
Shit!
可恶的蝙蝠!
Stupid bats!
没有汽油 中士 不过我找到了这个
No gas, sir, but I found this.
卫星电话 他们一定是通过 这个和基地联系的
Satellite phone. Must have been how they contacted base.
- 我想它可能已经坏了 - 见鬼 看来某人脾气不太好啊
- I don't think it's working. - Damn, somebody's got a temper.
哦 整个矿山都找遍了 中士 没人在
Oh, mine's all buttoned up, Sarge. Nobody's home.
- 那是谁的无线电? - 一定是他们中一个人的
- Whose radio is that? - Must be one of theirs.
威尔森 汉 你们在那儿么?
Wilson. Han. Are you there?
喂
Hello.
你到底是谁?
Who the fuck is this?
我是美国国民自卫队 杰弗雷·米尔斯通中士
This is Sergeant Jeffrey Millstone of the U. S. National Guard.
你是谁? 你的位置在哪儿?
Who is this, and what's your position?
我需要帮助
I need help.
你遇到危险了吗?
Are you in distress?
见鬼! 斯皮特 这玩艺儿的 接受范围有多远?
Fuck. Spitter, what's the range on these things?
方圆几英里吧 在视线范围之内
Couple miles. Line of sight.
中士!
Sarge!
像是反光镜打的信号
Looks like a signal mirror.
应该就是他了
It's got to be him.
我们来执行搜救任务
We're on a search and rescue mission.
- 我们现在不就在干嘛! - 你给我闭嘴!
- That's right we are! - Shut the fuck up!
我说是搜救任务 不是什么春假旅行
I said search and rescue, not fucking spring break.
我要你们在五分钟之内带好 武器和装备回到这儿来
I want you back here with weapons and gear for a climbing assault in five.
- 是 - 是 中士
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir, Sarge.
你觉得这样好么? 不和总部 联络就到那上面去?
Do you think it's a good idea going up there without contacting headquarters?
你喜欢和我顶着干 是吧? 拿破仑?
Do you like fucking with me, Napoleon?
我看你是喜欢这样 你知道吗
I think you do. You know what?
你的职责就是看守厕所…
You're officially in charge of guarding the latrine...
…不过不许用 只是看守它
not using it, but guarding it.
我要你单腿站立 把枪举过头顶…
I want you to stand on one leg and hold your rifle over your fucking head...
…要确保没人偷走马桶 或是在那儿捣乱!
and make sure that no one steals or molests that Port-a-Potty.
否则我马上把你送军事法庭严办!
Or I will have your Gomer Pyle ass court-martialed immediately.
你明白我对你说的话吗? 明不明白! ?
Do you understand what I am saying to you? Do you understand me! ?
好 我去 我只是觉得这主意不怎么样
Yeah, I'll go. I just think that it's a bad idea.
- 去给我看厕所去 现在就去! - 是 长官!
- Go and guard that fucking latrine, now! - Sir, yes, sir!
- 装实弹还是空包弹? - 每支枪装一枚实弹 它更重一些
- Live ammo or blanks? - One live mag each weapon. It's heavier.
还有手电和水合袋 多背些重量 对你们这帮胆小鬼有好处
Flashlights and hydration packs, too. The more weight, the better for you clowns.
训练已经过去了一半 可你们还是跟新兵没两样
You're halfway through your training and you look like a bunch of raw recruits.
简直是美国国民自卫队的耻辱!
You're a disgrace to the U. S. National Guard...
…真打起仗来 你们连五分钟也活不了!
and wouldn't last five minutes in combat!
单腿站立 戈默·派尔! (戈默·派尔越战中被送上军事法庭)
One leg, Gomer Pyle!
你们其余的人…
The rest of you...
…都给我上山去 不许再 傻笑了 快!
get your asses up that hill and wipe those silly smiles off your faces, now!
我们走!
Let's move!
单腿站着 派尔! 单腿站着!
One leg, Pyle! One leg.
你可真坏
You're so bad.
- 全队停下! 约翰逊! - 是?
- Company halt! Johnson! - Sir?
你留在这儿
You stay here.
斯皮特和我们一起走 你试试无线电 看能不能联络上什么人
Spitter's coming with us. Get on the main radio and try to raise somebody.
你要能找到医疗救助的话 那人活命的机会就大一些
If you can get through to a medvac, the guy'll have a hell of a better chance.
快去吧
Now move.
是 中士
Yes, Sarge.
别忘了写信哦
Don't forget to write.
快走! 向后转!
Get going! Turn around!
单腿站着!
One leg!
- 长大以后妈妈跟我说 - 长大以后妈妈跟我说
- When I grew up my momma said - When I grew up my momma said...
要不参军就别想活
If I wasn 't in the Army then I'd be dead...
我说"妈 快看看我"
I told her "Look at me now, Mom"
I told her "Look at me now, Mom...
"这就是错过舞会的结果"
That's what happens when you miss the prom"
单腿站啊 戈默·派尔!
One leg, Gomer Pyle!
呼救 呼救 这里是 国民自卫队杨基59号…
Mayday, mayday. This is the National Guard Yankee Five Niner...
…呼叫羽马平原基地 请派医疗救援过来 完毕
calling the Yuma Flats Base requesting a medvac, over.
喂?
Hello?
见鬼!
Shit.
呼救 呼救 这里是 国民自卫队杨基59号…
Mayday, mayday. This is the National Guard Yankee Five Niner...
…呼叫羽马平原基地 请派医疗救援过来 完毕
calling the Yuma Flats Base requesting a medvac, over.
这群搞科研的跑到这鬼地方 到底要干什么?
What the hell are scientists doing way the hell out here?
除了石头和响尾蛇 什么都没有
There's nothing but rocks and rattlesnakes.
是军事任务 傻瓜 而且肯定不关你的事
Army business, dumbass. And definitely none of your business.
- 可是 中士 我是一名士兵 - 所以你有权…
- But, Sarge, I am in the army. - Which gives you the right...
- 把嘴闭上 - 好 那我就把嘴闭上
- to shut the fuck up. - Okay, I'll just shut the fuck up then.
这儿应该有多少人?
How many people are supposed to be here?
我不清楚 也许到那上面问问他吧
I have no idea. Maybe we can ask him up there.
找到这家伙之后怎么办?
What are we supposed to do when we find this dude?
得看他伤得怎么样了 我们等救援 或者把他抬下山
That depends on how bad he is. We wait for a medvac or hump him down by hand.
我知道我不应该说话 中士 不过我希望他…
I know I'm not supposed to talk, Sarge, but I hope he...
- 见鬼! - 救命!
- Shit, man! - Help!
我抓住你了!
I got you!
快 把他拉上来 我抓住你了 米奇!
Come on. Pull him up. I got you, Mickey!
哦 真见鬼!
Oh, shit!
嘿
Hello.
- 见鬼了 - 你救了我一命 中士
- Shit. - You saved my life, Sarge.
嗯 对 人无完人嘛
Yeah, well, nobody's perfect.
- 这洞到底有多深? - 通到中国?
- How far down does that thing go? - China?
也许有一百英尺深 和上百年的历史
Could be a hundred feet deep, a hundred years old.
就等着把你陷进来了
Just waiting to suck your ass in.
所以要睁大你们的眼睛
So keep your eyes open.
这儿附近有很多老矿井 你脚腕怎么样了 米奇?
There's a lot of old mines around here. How's your ankle, Mickey?
嗯 没事儿 我很好 咱们走吧
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine. Let's go.
- 我们没时间再耽搁了 - 嘿 快点 中士 咱们走
- We cannot afford to slow down. - Hey, come on, Sarge. Let's go.
- 回营地去吧 - 嘿 别这样 中士
- Head back to base camp. - Come on, Sarge.
米奇 回营地去 就现在 这是命令
Mick, back to camp. Now. That's an order.
大家都看什么呢? 咱们继续走
What the fuck is everybody looking at? Let's keep moving.
去他的
Screw it.
你不应该那样
You're not supposed to do that.
这是任务啊
Duty calls.
呼救 呼救 这里是 国民自卫队杨基59号…
Mayday, mayday, this is the National Guard Yankee Five Niner...
…呼叫羽马平原基地 请派医疗救援过来 完毕
calling the Yuma Flats Base requesting a medvac, over.
呼救 呼救 这里是 国民自卫队杨基59号…
Mayday, mayday, this is the National Guard Yankee Five Niner...
…呼叫羽马平原基地 请派医疗救援过来 完毕
calling the Yuma Flats Base requesting a medvac, over.
哦 我操!
Oh, fuck! Fuck!
- 怎么了? - 马桶里有一只手!
- What? - There's a hand in the shitter!
- 什么? - 过来看看
- What? - Check it out!
操…
Fucking...
里面没有人啊
There's nobody in there.
在那下面
Down there.
- 那人是谁? - 谁知道呀 粪坑里的野人!
- Who was that guy? - Shitman the barbarian, I have no idea!
救救我!
Help me!
- 噢 伙计 - 上帝呀
- Oh, man. - Oh, God.
我都分辨不出这些岩石
I can't tell one rock from another.
是在那三块之间
It was between those three.
好像是唯一可以上去的路 就在那边
Seems like that's the only way up. Right there.
- 还不是太糟 - 是啊 哥们
- That ain't so bad. - No, man.
一点也不糟 除非你是只能蹿会跳的松鼠
Not so bad at all. If you're a fucking squirrel.
这些伤口是怎么回事?
What's with all these cuts?
我不知道
I don't know.
是谁干的?
Who did this to you?
他们就在这儿
They're here.
他们是谁?
Who's they?
这些伤口没有很深
None of the cuts were that deep.
- 大面积感染造成的 - 什么?
- Massive infection. - What?
是在马桶里泡的 那里面都是病菌
Shit stinks because it's full of pathogens.
不管是谁干的 他只想让这人慢慢地死掉
Whoever did this to him, wanted him to die slowly.
什么样的人能对别人做出这种事来?
What kind of person could do that to someone?
我真的不知道
I honestly don't know.
咱们走 德尔玛
Let's go, Delmar.
这就对了
There you go.
选好点!
Pick your spots!
找好缝隙
Find the creases.
抓到了! 抓到了!
You got it. You got it.
继续 我的好兵
Keep going, soldier.
这就对了 我就是这个意思 德尔玛!
There you go. That's what I'm talking about, Delmar!
很好! 很好!
All right! All right!
很好!
All right!
整一个蜘蛛侠
Spider-Man.
你真是他妈的有一套
You are officially a bad motherfucker.
斯汤普 你下一个上去 其余的人都做好准备
Stump, you're up next. The rest of you get your asses ready!
好 斯汤普 咱们走 开始行动
All right, Stump, let's go. Let's get it going.
德尔玛 你在这儿时是从哪儿走的?
Where'd you go from here, Delmar?
妈妈 我爱你
Love you, Mommy.
别急 慢慢来 但要选好点 斯汤普
Take your time but pick your spots, Stump.
- 混蛋! - 别紧张 中士说我们要出发了
- Asshole! - Easy. Sarge says we're moving out.
下次从我背后过来时 别一声不响的
Well, make some noise next time you come up behind me!
好 随便你 我只是捎个信而已
Yeah, whatever. I'm just the messenger.
女人哪
Chicks, man.
喂 喂 完毕
Hello. Hello, over.
喂! 喂 完毕
Hello! Hello, over.
你能跟他们接通么?
Can you get through to them?
无线电坏了
Radio sucks.
喂? 中士? 有人么?
Hello! Sarge? Anybody?
天哪!
Holy shit!
- 噢 上帝! - 噢 不 不 不!
- Oh, my God. - Oh, no, no, no, no!
- 上帝! - 见鬼!
- God. - Shit!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
妈的!
Fuck!
- 怎么了? - 你的枪呢?
- What? - Where's your rifle?
噢 上帝 不见了
Oh, God. It's gone.
上帝!
Oh, God!
- 咱们到那上面去 - 不 咱们别上那座山
- Let's just get up there. - No, we're not going up that hill.
我可不会躲在这儿等他们下来
I'm not hiding down here and waiting for them to come down.
怎么? 你害怕了?
What? You scared?
这跟害怕没关系
It's not about being scared.
那跟不要做出愚蠢甚至可能 致命的决定有关
It's about not making idiotic and possibly fatal decisions.
好吧 我忘了是和谁在说话了
Right, forgot who I was speaking to.
一位差点把自己小队的人炸飞的天才
The same genius who got his whole squad blown to hell.
你没听到他说什么吗? 有人在这里
Didn't you hear what he said? Someone is here.
你想和他一样死去吗?
You wanna die like him?
那我们就赶上其他人在一起
Let's just get up with the others.
喂? 中士?
Hello, Sarge?
喂 中士!
Hello, Sarge!
喂? 中士? 有人么?
Hello? Sarge? Anyone?
有人能听到我吗?
Can anybody out there read me?
- 拿破仑! - 什么?
- Napoleon! - What?
我不知道…
I don't know...
安玻!
Amber!
拿破仑!
Napoleon!
我打中他了?
I hit him?
米奇! 米奇!
Mickey! Mickey!
嘿 那是谁?
Hey, who was that?
米奇 出了点事 噢 上帝 你没事吧?
Mickey, something's going on. Oh, God. Are you all right?
嗯 只是把脚扭伤了
Yeah, I just twisted my ankle.
坚持一下
Hold on!
天哪! 他妈的!
Holy shit! Fuck!
坚持住! 坚持住 我抓到你了
Hold on! Hold on, I got you.
- 妈的! - 坚持住 我抓住你了!
- Shit! - Hold on, I got you!
快开枪打他! 打他!
Shoot the fucker! Shoot him!
- 打他! - 我看不见里面!
- Shoot him! - I can't see in there!
枪里没子弹!
I don't have a shot!
快救救我!
Fucking help me, man!
见鬼 我不能…
Goddamn it, I don't...
不! 别松手! 别松手!
Fuck! Don't let go! Don't let go!
米奇!
Mickey!
哥们 有些不对劲
Man, this is some bullshit.
什么?
What?
我好像听到了什么 是枪声
Thought I heard something. A shot.
这里是军事基地 人们到处开枪的
This is a military base. People are shooting all over the place.
我想声音是从营地那边来的 你们有谁和安玻联系过么?
I think it came from camp. Has anybody checked in with Amber recently?
米奇现在已经到下面了 你知道 他们在帐篷里…
Mickey's down there by now. You know, he's got her in a tent...
…做完全不同的另一种训练 你知道我什么意思…
and they're doing a whole other kind of training. Know what I mean?
- 中士 在那上面 - 我看见它了!
- Sarge, up there. - I see it!
又一个
Another one.
你们两个! 快点给我上来!
You two! Get your asses up here!
走吧
Come on.
喂!
Hello!
噢 不!
Oh, no.
红黑色高帮篮球鞋 啊? 尺码也和我的一样?
The red and black high-top Forces. What? And it's my size too?
这上面究竟发生了什么?
What the fuck is it doing way up here?
现在我们要是找到了另一个 可就有的忙了
Now, if we could only find the other one we'd be in business.
中士! 到这儿来!
Sarge! Over here!
中士!
Sarge!
他的头竟然!
Fuck is in his head?
- 大兵克兰克海德? 清理一下 - 见鬼
- Private Crackhead? Fish it out. - Shit.
"保尔·福斯特博士 国防部"
"Dr. Paul Foster, Department of Defense. "
看起来我们好像找到了 一位科研人员
Looks like we found one of our scientists.
上好子弹
Lock and load.
这种事不应该发生在军事基地
This isn't supposed to happen on an army base.
- 我们是在美国军事设施中 - 这地方有罗得岛那么大
- We're in a U. S. Military facility. - The size of Rhode Island.
要是有哪个混蛋要发疯 这可绝对是个好地方
If some asshole wants to go nuts, this is a damn good place to do it.
斯皮特 用无线电呼叫安玻
Spitter, get Amber on the radio.
洞勾 洞勾 安玻 我是斯皮特 你收到没有? 完毕
Stark nine, stark nine. Amber, this is Spitter. You read me? Over.
洞勾 洞勾 安玻 我是斯皮特r 你收到没有? 完毕
Stark nine, stark nine. Amber, this is Spitter. Read me? Over.
干扰太强了
There's too much interference.
中士 我们应该回到那下面
Sarge, we should go back down there.
安玻很好 她和米奇和拿破仑在一起
Amber's fine. She's got Mick and Napoleon.
- 救我 - 那是他们的无线电? 把它给我
- Help me. - That their radio? Let me have it.
雷丁上校 是你么?
Colonel Redding, is this you?
嘿 能听见我说话么?
Hello, can you hear me?
- 这不是以前听到的那个声音 - 也许是 也许不是
- That wasn't the same voice as before. - Maybe it was, maybe it wasn't.
可要是有人受伤的话 我们就该去救他
But if somebody's hurt, we're gonna help him.
那要是有人耍我们的话 也得把他揪出来
And if somebody is fucking with us, we're gonna find out who it is.
我告诉过你 这不是放春假
I've told you before, this isn't spring break.
不管怎样都要冒险 事情就是这样
One way or the other, lives are at stake. That's how it is.
克朗克 斯皮特 你们和我走前队 密茜 斯汤普 德尔玛…
Crank, Spitter, you stay with me on lead. Missy, Stump, Delmar...
…你们几个在后面 小心我们身后 保持警惕 保持机动
you bring up the rear. Watch our backs. Stay alert, and stay alive.
我们走
Let's move.
你听到什么了么?
You hear something?
我不知道 可能是只鸟?
I don't know. Maybe a bird?
- 把眼睛睁大点 - 好
- Keep your eyes open. - Okay.
那个到底是什么?
What the fuck was that?
见鬼!
Shit!
到底是什么…
What the fu...
不! 中士!
No! Sarge!
德!
D!
斯皮特! 妈的!
Spitter! Fuck!
噢 见鬼 中士!
Oh, fuck, man. Sarge!
是斯皮特 伙计
That was Spit, man.
- 中士! - 我不是有意的!
- Sarge! - I didn't mean to do that!
中士!
Sarge!
你受伤了吗? 受伤了吗?
You hurt? You hurt?
- 我不是有意这样做的 - 做什么?
- I didn't mean to do that. - Do what?
中士!
Sarge!
我们怎么办?
What do we do?
去给我把药箱拿过来
Go get me the medi-pack.
德! 药箱! 把它拿过来!
D! Medi-pack! Bring it over here!
操
Fuck, man.
怎么回事?
What happened?
我发誓 这家伙只是乱射 正好射中了斯皮特的背部
I swear, this dude just popped out of nowhere and he stabbed Spit in the back.
操 我不是故意的 操 他还好吗? 他好吗? 操
Fuck, man, I didn't mean to. Fuck, man, is he okay? Is he okay? Fuck!
中士?
Sarge?
中士? 撑住 呼吸 呼吸 中士
Sarge? Come on, breathe. Breathe, Sarge.
中士 要撑住
Sarge, stay with us.
我们需要什么?
What do we need?
你需要什么?
What do you need?
克朗克? !
Crank? !
密茜 你需要什么?
Missy, what do you need?
克朗克? ! 克朗克? ! 告诉他们 兄弟 告诉他们
Crank? ! Crank? ! Tell them, man, tell them.
这是次意外
It was an accident.
这他妈的是次意外
It was a fucking accident.
他们在搞我们
They're fucking with us.
这些家伙很聪明
These guys are smart.
安玻?
Amber?
米奇呢?
Where's Mickey?
小心你们脚下岩石间的洞
Watch between the rocks. Under your feet, too.
他们就是这么抓走米奇的?
That's how they got Mickey?
- 他们就是那么干的 - 天啊
- That's how they did it. - God.
什么东西?
What is it?
你看到什么了 德尔玛?
What do you see, Delmar?
没什么 我们就快到了
It's nothing. We're almost there.
好 伙计们 我们用绳索把中士放下去
All right, guys. Let's rig a line and get Sarge down.
我和他一起下去
I'm going down with him.
对不起 斯皮特 我不知道怎么打两个人的结
Sorry, Spit, I don't know how to rig for a two-man.
- 我也不知道 兄弟 - 我可以
- Yeah, me either, man. - I can do it.
好 开始吧
All right. All right, let's make it happen.
- 你需要两个 是吗? - 嗯
- You need two, right? - Yeah.
哦 还有一些卡宾枪
Oh, and a couple of those carabineers.
撑住他 撑住他
Prop him up. Prop him up.
你确定你所做的吗?
You sure you know what you're doing?
- 双套结 适合这个 - 你肯定?
- Double bowline. Right knot for the job. - You sure about that?
- 我曾经是老鹰侦查社团的 - 希望这能有用
- I was an Eagle Scout. - It better fucking hold.
加油 斯皮特 开始吧
Come on, Spit, let's do it.
准备好了吗? 好
You ready? All right.
对不起 斯皮特
I'm sorry, Spitter.
这是唯一的办法 如果他松开了 会直接掉出绳套
It's the only way. If he's loose, he'll fall out of his harness.
知道了吗?
Okay?
下面见 混蛋
See you down there, cabron.
好的 伙计
Okay, man.
放松 放松
Easy. Go easy.
- 好的 - 你可以的 斯皮特
- Okay. - You got it, Spitter.
好的 哥们 踩稳脚步 放松
All right, man, plant your feet. Take it easy.
对 斯皮特 你做的很好 踩稳脚步 伙计
Right there, Spitter. You got it. Plant-plant your feet, man.
- 你做的很好 斯皮特 - 多一点 多一点
- You're doing good, Spitter. - Little more. Little more.
拿破仑 从你的屁股里拿出你的拇指 快来帮我们
Napoleon, get your thumb out of your ass and help us out!
你感觉还好吗? 你看上去很好 伙计 保持住
You feel comfortable? You looking good, man. Keep it right there.
- 稍微慢一点 - 慢点 我快看不见了
- Slow it down a little bit. - Slow down, I'm about to lose visual.
慢点 斯皮特
Keep it slow, Spitter.
慢点 慢点
Y'all slow down. Slow down.
斯皮特! 斯皮特!
Spitter! Spitter! Spit!
- 怎么回事? - 靠
- What happened? - Shit.
怎么回事? 怎么回事?
What happened? What happened?
他死了
He's fucking dead, man.
- 他妈的怎么回事? - 他死了
- What the fuck happened? - He's fucking dead.
你他妈的结没用 你个说谎的混蛋
Your fucking knot didn't hold, you lying faggot!
- 绳子一定是断了 - 绳子没断
- The rope must've broke. - The rope didn't break.
- 对的 - 是被剪断的
- Exactly. - It was cut.
在这里我们要一个一个的被干掉了
Oh, man, we're getting picked off one by one here.
哦 你个混蛋
Oh, you motherfuckers!
你个混蛋死定了! 听到没?
You motherfuckers are dead! You hear me? !
死定了
Dead!
靠
Shit.
绳子呢?
Where are the ropes?
谁拿了余下的绳子?
Who's got the rest of the ropes?
我放在那里的
I put them up there.
不见了 不在这里
They're gone. They're not here.
没有绳子我们无法下去
We can't get down without the ropes.
到底是谁他妈的对我们干这些事?
Who the hell is doing all of this fucking bullshit to us?
不管这帮混蛋是谁 他们想要我们死
Whoever these fuckers are, they want us dead.
不 他们就是想把我们困在这里 认为这样我们就没机会了
No, that's where they want us. Thinking we got no chance.
让我们一起离开这里 大家想办法
We're gonna get out of this together. Let's think about that.
- 我们要怎么下去呢? - 一定有路的
- So how do we get down? - There's got to be a way.
他们能上来 我们就从同样的路下去
They got up here. We'll take the same way down.
小心脚步 下去的路可真长
Watch your step. It's a long way down.
见鬼
Damn!
- 你不会喜欢的 - 怎么了?
- You're not gonna like this. - What?
操!
Fuck, man!
又一个死胡同!
Another dead end!
我告诉过你了 没绳索我们无法下去
No way we're getting down without ropes. I told you!
我们往回走 去找其他的路
We go back and find another way.
哦 靠
Oh, shit.
德 为什么我们偏要 朝着奇怪的声音走?
D, why the fuck are we moving towards the weird noises?
- 给我闭嘴 - 你给我闭嘴 都是胡扯
- Just shut the hell up. - You shut the hell up. This is bullshit.
德!
D!
靠
Shit.
开枪吧
Go ahead and shoot.
- 快 紧急救助 - 快来
- Let's get some first aid. - Coming up.
拿破仑 注意后方
Napoleon, let's watch our backs.
雷丁上校?
Colonel Redding?
撑住 长官 我们会带你离开这里的
Just hang on, sir, okay? We're gonna get you out of here.
你们的指挥官呢? 你们的指挥官呢?
Where's your C. O? Where's your Commanding Officer?
他牺牲了
We lost him.
最好让我看一下这伤口 长官
Better let me see those wounds, sir.
你治不好的 天啊
You don't have a fucking clue! Jesus.
靠
Shit!
长官 如果你知道什么 现在是时候告诉我们
Sir, if you know something we should know, now's the time.
我只是需要一点证明
I just needed a little proof.
- 什么证明? - 这里怎么回事 上校?
- Proof of what? - What's going on here, Colonel?
并不是洞里…
It's not the fucks in caves...
…的鬼怪让我睡不着
halfway around the world that keep me up at night.
就在我们该死的基地上
Right here in the middle of our own goddamn base.
有人还生活在矿井里
People still living in the mines.
他们意味解决掉那些人了 但我知道还没有
They thought they got rid of them, but I knew they didn't.
你们知道这些混蛋吗?
You knew about these fuckers?
要是再给我一两个晚上
One or two more nights...
我就能让他们炸回到石器时代
I could have had them blown back to the Stone Age.
告诉我们该怎么做 上校 我们怎样才能离开这里?
Tell us what to do, Colonel. How do we get out of here?
那是个不错的问题 不是吗?
That's a good fucking question. Isn't it?
你们可以… 你们可以钻到洞穴里
You could... You could go down through the mines.
毫无疑问他们会杀了你们
Except they'd kill you for sure.
除了女人 你们几位女士…
All except the girls, you ladies...
他们会让你们活下来生育 让他们的数量恢复
they'll keep you alive for breeding. Trying to get their numbers back up.
什么?
What?
管他呢 混蛋 我们怎么爬下山?
Yeah, whatever, asshole. How do we get down this hill?
很简单
Simple.
不 不 不!
No, no, no!
他妈的这是怎么了? 他妈的究竟怎么回事?
What the fuck? What the fuck was that, man?
我不知道我还能承受多少
I don't know how much more of this I can take.
我真他妈害怕
I'm so fucking scared.
我们会熬过去的
We're gonna get through this.
我们会离开这里的 知道吗?
We're gonna make it out of here. Okay?
你这么认为?
You think?
必须出去 我是克莱德唯一的亲人了
Have to. I'm the only real family Clyde's got.
如果能再闻他头发的味道 我愿付出一切
Give anything just to smell his hair again.
你从不提起他
You never talk about him.
工作是工作 家庭是…我不知道 神圣的
Work's work. Family is, I don't know, sacred.
我一直把这两者区别对待
I always tried keeping the two separate.
但我现在认为这都是狗屁
But I guess that's all bullshit now.
爱你 妈咪
Love you, Mommy.
他真漂亮
He's beautiful.
开枪!
Now!
耶!
Yeah!
婊子!
Bitch!
他死了吗?
Is he dead?
操你妈的!
Fucking A!
抓到了
Got him.
你还好吗?
You all right?
在营地从我后面扑过来的 就是这个狗屎
That's the piece of shit that jumped me back at camp.
我认为就是他杀死了米奇
I think he killed Mickey, too.
靠 真他妈的丑
Damn. He's fucking ugly.
真他妈臭
Fucking stinks.
真他妈的大
He's fucking big, man.
没有热弹不能解决的
Still, nothing a little hot lead can't fix.
热弹? 听听你说的 哥们
Hot lead? Listen to you, man.
嗯 这只是一个 还剩多少?
Yeah, well, it's just one. How many are left?
让他们来吧
Bring them on, man.
- 你们做的很棒 - 谢谢
- You guys did good. - Thanks.
闻起来像屎一样
Smells like shit.
密茜呢?
Where's Missy?
嘿 密茜?
Hey, Missy?
- 密茜? - 靠!
- Missy? - Shit!
那里!
There!
小心你们自己
Watch yourselves.
密茜!
Missy!
等等 德尔玛
Hold on, Delmar.
你刚才听到那哥们说了吗 我们该下去 兄弟
You heard what that dude said. We should climb down, man.
你说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
说你和我的性命 我们不需要绳子
Talking about you and me. We don't need ropes.
我们可以自由式攀下去 毫不费力的 我们下去吧
We can get down freestyle, no sweat, man. Let's just do it.
- 那其他人怎么办? - 密茜怎么办?
- What about the rest of us? - What about Missy?
我们可以很快的下去 你知道的
We can get down fast and you know it.
其他人呆在原地 我们会回来帮忙
The rest of you guys just hang tough and we're gonna bring back some help.
操!
Fuck that!
我们一起行动 这是最好的办法 我们分开…
We stick together. It's the best way. We separate...
- 我们就死定了 - 你说的对
- We're dead. - You got that right.
斯汤普
Stump.
我要去搏一下 兄弟
I'm gonna take my chances, man.
斯汤普 跟我们呆在一起
Stump! Stay with us, man.
拜托
Come on.
我下去后 我会回来帮忙的
When I get down, I'm gonna bring back help.
这太愚蠢了 兄弟
This is stupid, man.
克朗克 那才愚蠢
Crank, that is fucking stupid, man.
我要出去了
I'm going back out.
靠
Shit.
你们都准备好了吗?
You guys ready for this?
我们跟在你后面
We got your back.
这里好臭
It stinks in here.
你看到什么了吗?
You see anything?
他们只有一条路能走
There's only one way they could've gone.
死胡同?
Dead end?
他妈的他们在哪里?
Where the fuck are they?
伙计们
Guys.
下面
Down here.
没看见什么
I can't see shit.
我去检查下
I'll check it out.
等我信号
Wait for my signal.
- 你还好吗? - 没事了
- You good? - Clear.
靠! 靠!
Fuck! Fuck!
靠!
Fuck.
哦 靠
Oh, shit.
哦 我的天那
Oh, my God!
接到了
We got you.
- 弄我出去 - 你没事 一点没事
- Get me out! - You're good. You're fine. It's all right.
天啊
Jesus Christ!
你还好吗? 拿破仑
You cool, Napoleon?
我想是的 天那
Yeah, I think so. Jesus.
我们到底是在哪里?
Where the hell are we?
又下了一层
Next level down.
好
All right. Okay.
靠!
Fuck!
他妈的只是些石头
They're just fucking rocks.
只是些石头而已
They're only fucking rocks.
我不会让你们这些混蛋抓到我的 不会是我 不会是今天
I'm not gonna let you bastards get me. Not me. Not today.
这不可能发生
This is not gonna happen.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
有微风
There's a breeze.
靠
Shit.
这就是那帮混蛋切断绳子的地方
This is where the fuckers hid to cut the ropes.
我们不能就这么把他们丢在下面
We can't just leave them down there.
我们现在无能无力
There's nothing we can do for them now.
除了找到密茜然后离开这鬼地方
Except find Missy and get the fuck out of here.
密茜有可能也死了
Missy's probably dead, too.
那么说对谁都没好处
You're not doing anybody any good talking like that.
加油
Come on.
德尔玛!
Delmar!
不 救救我! 哦 天那!
No, help me! Oh, God!
哦 不! 不!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
是个死胡同?
Is it a dead end?
不 能穿过
No. No, it goes through.
- 有多深? - 去看看
- How deep is it? - Let's see.
你认为他们有多少人?
How many do you think there are?
谁知道 太多了
Who knows? Too many.
- 你在干吗? - 我给我自己留一颗
- What are you doing? - I'm saving one for myself.
你还记得克朗克说的吗? 没有比死亡更糟的了
Do you remember what Crank said? Dead is never better.
我们会离开这里的
We're gonna get out of here.
我只是…
I just...
- 安玻! - 拿破仑!
- Amber! - Napoleon!
- 撑住! - 靠!
- Hang on! - Shit!
靠!
Fuck!
到底是什么? !
What the hell? !
靠!
Shit!
你们还好吗?
You guys all right?
安玻? !
Amber? !
拿破仑? !
Napoleon? !
我的来复枪呢?
Where's my rifle?
你还好吗?
You okay?
- 靠! - 安玻!
- Shit. - Amber!
你们还好吗?
You guys all right?
嗯 我们还好
Yeah. We're all right.
- 我们去找一条下来的路 - 没问题
- We're gonna find a way down. - No problem.
撑住
Hang on.
靠
Shit.
拿破仑
Napoleon.
你在干吗?
What are you doing?
拿破仑!
Napoleon!
我好像听到什么
I thought I heard something.
靠
Shit.
我认为他们就在这一层
I think that's the level they're on.
你认为我们没有装备能爬下去吗?
You think we can climb down without gear?
你看到那个梁了吗? 如果能把它弄过来 就可以滑下去
You see that beam? If we can make it across, we slide down that.
我认为我可以跳过去
I think I could make that jump.
你干吗?
What are you doing?
克朗克 克朗克! 等等!
Crank. Crank! Wait!
- 克朗克! - 妈的! 靠!
- Crank! - Fuck! Shit!
靠!
Shit!
德尔玛!
Delmar!
撑住!
Hang on!
谢谢
Thanks.
我们继续向前
Let's keep it moving.
走
Let's go.
不!
No!
想要
Want.
妈妈
Mama.
漂亮
Pretty.
臭婊子!
Dirty cunt!
过来
Come here.
我的!
Mine!
好甜
So sweet.
不 是她 爸爸 不
No. Was her. Papa, no.
你给我孩子
You give me baby.
- 靠 - 该死 快
- Shit. - Goddamn it. Come on.
混蛋!
Motherfucker!
密茜!
Missy!
救我!
Help me!
谁来救我!
Somebody help me!
靠! 是斯汤普的头巾
Shit. It's Stump's headband.
什么?
What?
哦 我的天 靠
Oh, my God. Oh, shit.
他在哪里?
Where is he?
那里!
There!
抓到你了
Got you.
够了!
Enough!
把他们全杀了
Kill them all.
拿破仑? 我们该走了 他有枪 快
Napoleon? We got to go. He's got a gun. Come on.
拿破仑
Napoleon.
舱门 关舱门 关舱门
The hatch. Get the hatch. Get the hatch!
密茜? !
Missy? !
哪条路?
Which way?
在这里你们很安全
You safe here.
安全
Safe.
我在你后面 我们走
I'm right behind you. Let's go.
该死
Goddamn.
这里到底发生了什么?
What the hell happened here?
来啊 婊子
Come on, bitch!
耶 宝贝! 只是子弹多少的问题! 一定要多射几颗
Yeah, baby! It's all about volume! Got to have volume!
是克朗克
It's Crank.
- 你还好吗? - 我很好 我很好
- You okay? - I'm all right. I'm all right.
肩部受伤 没有伤到骨头
Lone Ranger shoulder wound. Missed the bone completely.
见鬼
Damn.
- 你还好吗? - 嗯
- You good? - Yeah, yeah.
你在跟谁搞鬼呢 啊? 你在跟谁搞鬼?
Who you fucking with, huh? Who you fucking with?
克朗克? 克朗克? 你还剩有弹药吗?
Crank? Crank? You got any ammo left?
靠
Fuck.
我也没了
I'm out, too.
德尔玛? 你的刺刀
Delmar? Your bayonet.
- 克朗克! 德尔玛! - 靠!
- Crank! Delmar! - Shit!
下来
Down here.
哦 靠 你们还活着!
Oh, shit! You guys are alive!
你们怎么了?
What happened to you?
- 哦 靠 - 德尔玛 你还好吗?
- Oh, shit. - Delmar, are you all right?
出去了就一切都好了
Be a hell of a lot better when we get out of here.
- 你被击中了? - 我很好 没什么
- Were you shot? - I'm fine. It's nothing.
你确定?
You sure?
靠
Shit.
- 那到底是什么? - 他没什么的
- What the hell is that? - He's okay.
你他妈疯了吗? 他是他们其中之一
Are you out of your goddamn mind? He's one of them!
不 他刚才救了我们的命
No, he just saved our lives.
不用怕 你们来
No fear. You come.
跟我来
Follow me.
来
Come.
这边
This way.
- 你好吗? - 我没事
- You good? - I'm all right.
不要担心 我没事
Don't worry. I'm all right.
我们必须把他弄出这里
We got to get him out of here.
密茜并不远 你听到过她的叫喊了
Missy's not that far. You heard her screams.
没有弹药我们怎么把她带离这里?
How're we gonna get her out of here without any goddamn ammo?
我们可以用石头和枪柄来跟他们搏斗
We can fight them with rocks and rifle butts if we have to.
- 谁被兰博附体了吗? - 我只是想把所有人都带离这里
- Who's Rambo resurrected now? - I just wanna get everyone out of here.
是吗? 那就去告诉 米奇、斯皮特还有斯汤普吧
Yeah? Well, tell that to Mickey, and Spitter, and Stump!
- 克朗克! 他妈的闭嘴 - 你相信那家伙?
- Crank! Shut the hell up! - You trust that guy?
他帮我们藏起来了 没有把我们交出去
He hid us from them. He didn't give us up.
我们别无选择 不得不相信他
We don't have any choice. We have to trust him.
胡扯! 天知道他会把我们带去哪里
Bullshit! God knows where he's taking us.
跟你老实讲 我不相信 老天会知道这个地方
To be honest with you, I'm not sure God knows anything about this place.
穿过这里
Through here.
必须穿过这里
Must through here.
天那
Jesus.
靠
Shit.
我靠
Holy shit.
哦 伙计
Oh, man.
哦 天啊
Oh, God.
- 天那 - 这他妈的都是什么啊? !
- Jeez! - What the fuck? !
- 天啊! 米奇! - 不要去看!
- God! Mickey! - Don't look!
你个恶心的混蛋!
You sick fuck!
该杀了你! 我该杀了你!
You should be shot! I should kill you!
- 克朗克! - 怎么 伙计?
- Crank! - What, man?
你为什么老是 和我作对 德尔玛 啊?
Why you always try to shut me down, Delmar, huh?
不要发狂
Don't freak out.
- 他妈的怎么了? - 不要发狂
- What the fuck? - Don't freak out.
不要发狂 不要发狂
Don't freak out. Don't freak out.
等等 等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
他妈的怎么了 什么? 德尔玛
What the fuck, what? Delmar!
德尔玛
Delmar.
怎么了 伙计?
What the fuck, man?
你被击中了两次?
You were hit twice?
为什么你不告诉我?
Why didn't you tell me?
不要 伙计 千万别!
Don't do this, man. Don't do this!
别这样 不要离开我 兄弟
Don't do this. Don't leave me, man.
他妈的不要离开我
Don't fucking leave me!
靠!
Fuck!
给我医药包 拿破仑
Get me a medi-pack. Napoleon!
给我医药包 快点
Get me a medi-pack. Come on.
克朗克
Crank.
我不会丢下他的
I'm not gonna leave him.
我不会丢下他的 你个变态
I'm not gonna leave him. You sick fuck!
- 你不会得到他的 - 好 好
- You're not gonna have him! - Okay, okay.
我会带你离开这里的
I'm gonna get you out of here.
带我们离开这里
Get us out of here.
来
Come. Yeah.
我会带你离开这里的
I'll get you out of here.
哦 耶! 哦 耶!
Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
我打赌这就是通向外面的 怎么才能打开这该死的门?
I bet this leads outside! How do I get this fucking door open?
- 快点! - 嘿 算了吧 克朗克
- Come on! - Hey, would you forget it, Crank?
算了吧 这是个防护门 你根本打不开
Would you forget it? It's a blast door. You're never gonna get it open.
见鬼!
God dammit!
我们要离开这里 你个混蛋
We need to get out of here, you fucking retard!
- 克朗克! - 我们怎样才能离开这里?
- Crank! - How the fuck do we get out of here?
密茜怎么办?
What about Missy?
你能不能打消密茜还活着这个念头? 密茜已经死了 明白不?
Would you get off this shit that she's alive? Missy is fucking dead! Okay? !
就像其他人一样
Just like the rest of them.
如果我们不离开这里 那我们也一样
Just like we're gonna be if we don't get the fuck out of here!
不找到她我们不离开这地方
We are not leaving this place without her!
愚蠢 知道吗?
Stupid, okay?
我们怎样才能离开这里? 哪条路能出去?
How the fuck do we get out of here, man? Which way is it? !
那边是什么? 那边是什么?
What's over there? What's over here?
- 我回去找她 - 安玻 待在这里
- I'm going back for her! - Amber, stay here.
- 伙计们! - 安玻?
- Guys! - Amber?
哦 靠! 伙计们 来看啊
Oh, shit! Guys! Check it out!
正是我们需要的…
Everything we need...
不要碰! 不要碰!
No touch! No touch.
安玻! 求你了 别
Amber! Please, don't.
我求你了
I'm begging you.
我会回来找你的
I'd go back for you.
安玻!
Amber!
哦 耶! 哦 耶! 哦 靠!
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, shit.
炸药 太棒了
Dynamite. Perfect.
我的天啊 终于我可以离开这里了
My God. I'm gonna get out of here after all.
哦 耶 德尔玛? 我们要离开这里了 宝贝
Oh, yeah. Delmar? We're getting out of here, baby.
怎么了…
What the...
靠!
Fuck!
哦 天那 克朗克!
Oh, God. Crank!
- 你还好吗? - 嗯
- You okay? - Yeah.
哦 靠 克朗克!
Oh, shit. Crank!
克朗克?
Crank?
克朗克!
Crank!
是密茜!
It's Missy!
我们行动吧
Let's do it.
密茜的电话
Missy's phone.
- 什么? - 你还有密茜的电话吗?
- What? - Do you still have Missy's phone?
等在这里
Wait here.
我再也受不了了 我不想安静
I can 't take it anymore. I can 't! I don 't wanna be quiet.
我要离开这里 我们会死的 你不明白吗? 我们会死的
I want out of here. We're gonna die, don 't you get it? We're gonna die!
哪条路?
Which way to go?
哪条路 拿破仑? 哪里?
Which way do we go, Napoleon? Where?
我再也受不了了 拿破仑 受不了了
I can 't take it anymore, Napoleon. I can 't!
天才
Genius.
我们会死的 你不明白吗? 我们会死的
We're gonna die, don 't you get it? We're gonna die!
天啊
Jesus Christ.
- 安玻! - 你还好吗? 把手给我
- Amber! - You okay? Give me this arm.
- 和我待在一起 - 没事 我们找到你了
- Stay with me. - It's okay. We got you. We got you.
其他人呢?
Where's everybody else?
我们会死的
We're gonna die.
爱你 妈咪
Love you, Mommy.
求你带我离开这里
Get me out of here, please!
- 不要再让他碰我 - 快 我们走
- Don't let him touch me again. - Come on, let's go.
求你 不要再让他碰我
Please. Don't let him touch me.
- 安玻 - 快点
- Amber. - Come on.
- 我们终于找到你了 - 这边
- We got you. - This way.
拿破仑!
Napoleon!
- 我听不到他动静了 - 你在干吗?
- I don't hear him anymore. - What are you doing?
我们快离开这里
Let's just get out of here!
求你了
Please!
我们没时间了…
We don't have time...
过来!
Come here!
- 不! - 死!
- No! - Die!
婊子!
Bitch!
死!
Die!
拿破仑 站起来! 站起来!
Napoleon, get up! Get up!
拿破仑 站起来!
Napoleon, get up!
死
Die.
安玻!
Amber!
死 死 死 死
Die. Die. Die. Die. Die.
快 快
Come on. Come on!
- 拉好她 - 密茜 我们走 快离开这里
- Get her! - Missy, let's go! Let's get out of here!
混蛋!
Motherfucker!
密茜 快! 密茜!
Missy! Come on! Missy!
不要让他拿到他的刀
Don't let him get his knife!
- 拉! - 密茜!
- Pull! - Missy!
抓住我的腿! 哦 我的天啊
Get my leg! Oh, my God!
放开她
Let go of her!
密茜! 去拿武器!
Missy! Get something!
密茜!
Missy!
哦 我的天啊
Oh, God.
国民自卫队训练兵和他们中士的失踪 从未向他们的家人解释过
官方把他们列为擅离职守
16区仍然是被认为不存在的